CURRICULUM VITAE OF EVANGEL CHIGOZIE ALAEGBU

1. Personal Data		
Subject	Information	
Name (Surname Last)	Evangel Chigozie Alaegbu	
Date of Birth	30th January 1984	
Sex	Male	
Marital Status	Married	
State of Origin	Imo State	
Local Government Area	Ehime - Mbano	
Nationality	Nigerian	
Telephone Number	08069752912, 08095555992.	
Email Address	angelbrain2002@yahoo.com, softwareking101@gmail.com	
Contact Address	House C18A Road Safety Estate Lokogoma Abuja.	
Office Address	House D5 Salatu Royal Estate Aminu Kano Crescent Wuse II	
	Abuja.	
Residential Address	House C18A Road Safety Estate Lokogoma Abuja.	

PROFILE SUMMARY	A self-motivated, articulate, focused and achievement-oriented	
	individual with extensive knowledge of IT services as a systems	
	administrator, tester and programmer, my practical experience	
	includes system administration, support, software development,	
	testing, specifications, security policy and computer repairs and	
	installation, computer and mobile software development testing and	
	management, Strong commercial skills in performance	
	improvement and delivering accurate and timely software and	
	system reporting.	

AREAS OF EXPERTISE > Software development testing. > Web and Program development. > Mobile Application development and management. > Accounts Software/Reports. > Software and hardware Maintenance. > Business Analysis. > Maintaining Systems by monitoring and correcting software defects. > Evaluating software and systems that make computer and hardware work effectively and efficiently. > Following up on business communications, billing, and ordering.

Cyber security and Technology.Financial Management software.ICT Solutions and consultancy.

2. Work Experience			
Organisation	Address	Position Held	Period
Resident Fintech	No 38 Mike Akhigbe way Jabi Fct-Abuja	Head IT/ISMS	2020-
Limited		Manager	
Vangitech Limited	Suite 15 Tripple F plaza Wuye Fct - Abuja	ICT Manager	2019-2020
Biovangel Digital	14 Road House 6 D Close Efab Estate	MD/CEO	2016-2018
Limited	Lokogoma Abuja		
H Communication	Block C1B Emab Plaza Wuse II Abuja	Digital	2014-2015
Limited		Marketing	
		Director	
Double A Global	Plot 3 & 4 Trans Amadi Industrial Layout	Outlet Manager	2013-2014
Resources Limited	Port Harcourt River State.	_	

3. Educational Qualifications			
Institution	Address	Certificate Obtained	Period
University of Abuja	Gwagwalada, Abuja	Bachelor of Science in Computer Science (BSC)	2007-2011
University of Abuja	Gwagwalada, Abuja	Ordinary National Diploma in Business Admin (OND)	2005-2006
Government Science Secondary School Pyakasa	Pyakasa Along Airport Road, Abuja	West African Examinations Council (WAEC)	1998-2003

LEA Primary School	Zuba, Abuja	First	School	Leaving	1993-1997
Zuba		Cert			

5. National Youth Service Corps (NYSC)			
Organisation Address Period			
Exempted		2012	

6. Other Certifications			
Organisation	Address	Certificate	Period
		Obtained	
A4S	NO 2 Bamisile Street, Off Allen Lane,	Lead Implementer in	2020
	Ikeja Lagos.	ISMS,	
		IN/6263/53632	
A4S	NO 2 Bamisile Street, Off Allen Lane,	Lead Auditor in	2020
	Ikeja Lagos.	ISMS,	
		TH/20/201461	
A4S	4S NO 2 Bamisile Street, Off Allen Lane, Awa		2020
	Ikeja Lagos.	TH/20/201461	

REFERENCE

NAME	ADDRESS	MOBILE NUMBER
Mrs. Ukairo Happiness Chibozo	Airforce Primary School	08038904841
	Portharcourt	
	(Ministry of Defense)	
Colonel. Vincent Egbulem	Wubassy Barracks Officers	08095443925
	Living Quarters Abuja	
Mr. Oliver Ehieze	Nigeria Immigration	08033957513
	Service Owerri	